Okay, hello. This is the second of two
very special classes for this week.
This tradition goes back to Alexandrow,
the head of the Guadalajara group.
He asked me to sprinkle in a
little dessert between the Deal on the Ring
classes, just to give you
new material to think about. So,
like the second of the dessert
classes, I always
include something we probably have
n't heard before, and also a
bit more difficult material.
So if you were already lost in the Chamber class,
then you'll feel
even more lost in this class.
So don't worry, it really is a
special class.
We go very, very deep.
[Music]
Yeah, I'm going to do the gravel episode.
We have more. I've never heard of it before, so don't worry.
I
promised to teach you Ross.
Someone showed me the great cathedral in
Mexico City.
I can't remember anything in the
cathedral because the front yard was a
chance shoe factory.
I've never
seen such a beautiful place in my life. Stanley, are
you ready? That
means these  Head discussion,
this is now the five minutes before the break.
A few very, very intelligent people are
asking me if everything comes from seeds, if
everything is caused by chambers,
and then I say yes, everything
comes from chambers. And then the
next question is, does karama come from cardamom?
Who made chambers?
How can it be that if you give someone
something, you get more back
for yourself? And we're
presenting the answer now, and then
we'll start with the profound class.
This is a shock. So, let's say I
have another jump and I like shooting,
but he also likes Ross, and we
only have one thing: I'm not a
spiritual
person, I'm not a bodyguard,
I'm not a kind, I'm not Adria,
I'm not on the way either. I'm
just a completely normal person, and I like
Chorus, and I want the guarantee that
I'll also be ahead in the future. What
should I do with the goal now?
I actually wanted to give it to him.
Why didn't I shoot? You're not
spiritual, forget it. It's just
about wanting more.
Forget the spiritual, I'm
selfish, I like taste, I just want
this to happen, get as many goals
as possible, how do I guarantee
the future tastelessness now, I
have to give it to him,
and then I have a question for you, his
and my mouth, no, we're
not going to get into that yet, it's his
and my mouth, visually speaking, no, because
his mouth is meters away, his mouth
is banished, and my mouth is here, the main
square for here, the Danube asks,
how do you recognize a hippie, everything is
one, everything is one, but it's not true,
he's over there, I'm here,
we even expressed that in words,
he and I, his mouth
and my mouth, we even have
different words for it,
and I know that the only way to get
more dead is the only way to get rid of it, to
give it into other people's mouths, so the only way to get rid of it
in this and to get
the show in someone else's mouth,
that's the only way to get an
office in this and to get it,
you've already worked  Visually,
this mouth is a meter away,
but functionally, the gate must have
these lips across. If I want to have a shot in
my lips, if there's no show
between these lips,
then the office will go into the lips,
functionally, not visually. We
most colorful don't trust these two eyes.
We take the third one here, this known pig.
If I were big in
this and gave, then definitely, definitely, definitely, definitely
more will go on
in this and come functions. Is
this mouth my mouth? Hermund of
Stanley is the mouth of Nike and
Michael's mouth is because with mouth and the
hippies in the Danube, not
everything is a 2. We are all a
Garmisch. It was, I have to put something in
his mouth so that I get something in
my mouth,
and something happens with the language at that point.
All languages ​​in this world were
developed. All languages ​​in this world
were developed by people who
have no idea about chambers.
So if you really look deeper into this with the Coro,
then you have a
real problem. Mike Sendall lives, there
is something similar, and that's why
his purchase decision...  Stanley
gave Michael a chapel and because there was
no comeback, Sally also got a
microphone, understood, and I think
that's the reason why we ca
n't talk to our brothers.
If you kick a Buddha,
hey Stanley, Milan, Rome,
what's Sandro doing here? Have you been here before?
If pressure is applied,
we won't be able to understand them.
And what was the question when we
started eating?
Who makes karama? Why does he get it like that when
you leave? Because you don't give. I didn't give anything in the
end.
I gave Michael something,
understood
why it worked? It's a
false idea that Michael gets something
because he never gave anything.
Michael got a goal because he gave
Michael a school start. You don't have to be a
genius to say that. Hey,
tombstone word, Maigler got his Giro.
Here it went, he got a goal,
but how did he do that? He had already received it,
but how? Tell me, we already received it.
Understand that Michael got it, why?
Because Mike Lynch
received euros. It's so obvious
and that's why it worked.
And if he were separated from me,
if he weren't Michael, then
karma wouldn't work. If I gave
Michael something, he
naturally gets it. It's so simple that it's
really difficult. So if
someone asks you who makes it
work, karma needs such a leap,
ready to be, must be ready.
And so that we all have shows,
it's a mouth. I'm thinking of Dro. A
Spaniard gave another mouth,
and that's why others got a boost. Visually,
I gave it to people.
Functionally, we are the same person. Understood? Thank you, thank you,
Sandy, the duo who ate for me.
And now we're going to do
something even more confusing. So,
five years ago, I promised guys in Indonesia that I would
write a book about the council's life. They
understood that I would
finish it in three months. Then I
started taking more notes, and
after 1000 pages,
five years later, they forgot
who I actually was. And it took
me a long time to
re-establish contact because
half of the contacts have since died. And
I'm donating the money,
fighting, and the program is
next month.  I believe I'll be
on this beautiful island
in Indonesia for two days on August 24th, and there's this mountain there.
Please, please come! You are most
welcome.
And now, unfortunately, I've
found my book, "For Those Who
Can Speak Tibetan,"
by Nana Shi, the one who also wrote the book
about logic in Tibet. It's the most famous book on logic in Tibet. He
also wrote a commentary on the
Wheel of Life, and we
found it. I'm eating it right now; it's
354 pages long, which is very long. He
explains the Wheel of Life in a
really sexy way, and I thought
you might like to hear excerpts.
He uses a book by Mattea Meyer. He
's the coming Butterhead. He's supposed to
come to
this world very, very soon. And then there were
some holy names for him.
He lived 1700 years ago, and he
decided to practice two Janas,
like the people of Guadalajara decided to do.
And then he started the
first section of the Wheel of Life two years ago.
What is that? The first one.  The first step
is to make contact with the angels.
11. In the cave, he learned the mantra of "My
Prayer to the Coming Mother." This
is a typical practice in retreat,
and he's already done, for example, 14 million times in retreat.
What is the meaning of a mantra that
you write to an angel? Please come finally.
And some are quite
stubborn. You have to ask them 1.4 million times
before they come.
It's like when the priest says to you, "
Pray 14 million times, monkey Mary." When he
proposed to my daughter
[Music]
in the cave,
I think he stayed in the cave for twelve years or so,
and he kept going. He did it, though:
please come, please come, please come.
Nothing happened, and then he got really
upset. He got really angry. This does
n't work, this method does
n't work, and he gave up on Vanessa.
Then he decided to go to the city,
and it was probably in the bar
on the way to the city,
but on the side of the road, he saw a dog,
and the dog was
run over by a horse-drawn cart, and that...  The wheel
ran over the dog's belly, and
since the belly was slashed open, all
the entrails were lying around. If you've ever been there,
you know what it's like, and there were
ten million flies flying everywhere.
And when I showed him, I had to take him
to the vet now. When
I bent down to
pick up the dog,
we saw how
many maggots were already in the entrails
from the flies. He thought to himself, "If I pick them up
now,
and if we put the dog's belly back up,
all these maggots will die."
What can I do now?
Maybe with a razor blade,
I'll make a slit in my thigh,
and then I'll take the worms and
put them in my thigh. Nice
fresh blood.
And then he got a knife
and slashed his thigh,
and then reached inside the dog, took
out the first maggot, and kept it so he
could put it in his thigh.
Or that's how you do it.
I think it's really
unpleasant for them; their
fingers are too strong for that.
I need the softer one, I'll take my tongue, it
's very soft, and I'll take them out
one by one with
my tongue and
put them in my thigh because the bond is tight,
but I'm trying, I can do this.
He closed his eyes
and touched the ground with his tongue,
then he opened his eyes
and there it was. Turn around, homeland,
yes, you did come,
yes, I worked for twelve years and
you didn't come,
and then I gave up,
I went back into the world and he showed
himself as the dog. What's wrong with you?
I waited for twelve years,
you didn't come. I
called your name 1.4 million times, where were
you? I was in the cave the whole time,
I missed you every time. When it was
over, when you... when you... when you...
portal...
you know how... spat on me like that.
I was there in the cave, trying harder,
that was going.
I was always around you,
but you didn't have enough good karma
to see me,
and now you...  Real sympathy for
this dog and for the maggots and
because of this good chamber you can
see me now and the manga says come I'll
put you on my shoulder and then
he put Dreher on his shoulder
and they turned the city I
saw Andrea and in the city there were
only 15,000 people
and 14 in 1999 in this city saw a
crazy person who had a dog on
his shoulder
[Music]
and then there was an old woman with
really good came and she was sitting on the
terrace and there said warranty
over developer found and they went into
the kitchen during the house
looked at their daughter
more than that strange thing happened
what happened when the guy on the
street and shouts I have Andrea I
found my trainer and on the
shoulder have dog with its guts hanging out
one person have enough
Khama the dog to see all the others
light saw
and then my Dreher said so that
his brother took him paradise and
as an angler he please teach
me what is the  The second step of
Panzer der Engel shows you how to become an
angel. He's doing the second
stage of the crime scene in my dream heaven in
about a month. Father taught him five
books. When my trainer van
Gaal came home, he dropped off the old material back
home. He
realized Anka's heart years older. A
month in butter paradise.
One of the five books as a jewel of
knowledge. It's 75 pages long and it's heart-
shaped.
Every person has to memorize it when they're ten years
old or so. So
the Gajic course builds 25 years. The first
twelve years, half the course in
this little book, the 75 pages, on the
market. We work 18 hours a
day. Every year we negotiate six
pages.
It's so difficult, it's so profound.
And today we're starting with material like how
he describes the wheel of life,
and then the body goes into a
very special meditation. It's
like, I don't know the English word. It's like,
you don't have to say it, it's not
the  noise also the same word
is used for supermodels slightly
[music]
posing to show off
I'll give you now the definition
of it
I was really interested why
they call the meditation of a boat something like that
lion behavior lions
posing the reading posing so why is it called
lions posing
normally a lion in the jungle doesn't have to be afraid
of other animals
when I did my three-year retreat as if
the first time were there to
send the place so a
farmer with 20,000 hectares with 7,000 hectares
we asked him if we could
fight on his land for three years at the small tent
and he agreed
and the next time she met him he had
broken his leg what happened and he told
me what he rode with his horse
and it goes up
he said the land of which I
wanted to give you
there lives the grandfather of all
rattlesnakes and they are so thick so long
and in the first proof of your land
for us exactly  We looked at it and
slept in the tent, and I lay
on the outside of the tent for a long time and read.
I was cold for a long time
[music]
and the whole tent was like that. On the first day, when
I was always filming, he
came and watched me.
He was also slithering around a tree,
and he loved
watching us. And Vaart said he did
n't need to be afraid, the grandfather
snake doesn't waste venom on
large creatures. If they have a rabbit,
then yes, they can eat it.
He is very, very experienced. He would put a
little venom in his mouth, and then
he starts, and then you see how the
rabbit disappears. And WDR Equipment
was very brave.
Petra S. pulled the rabbit out of the snake's throat by its ears. By the ears,
she pulled it out. The
rabbit
survived, but one foot was
already attacked by the stomach acid.
He lived for a long time after that. How long did Jack
Miller live? He lived with us for several years,
says the rabbit.
How can it be that long?  Bad
behavior,
we have so many snakes in May,
Marita Weier, five
snakes in the field in one night, you look at them,
ComCom, what, what, what can you do to me, have
yourself, set,
he burns away from me, set, cow, what do
you want, they have, really, this attitude, they
run from nothing, you ca
n't drive them away,
and that's exactly what's described here,
that's the lion, they're not
afraid of anything,
which means that the person who has
reached this level of meditation, the
apprenticeship directly from it,
and how do they go, they have just
experienced the apprenticeship, and we are a
bodyguard,
so if you eliminate the three negative feelings
that are caused by the drivers through the direct
warning of the majority, there are
80,000 bad karma here, that gives
84,000 negative thoughts, and if you
drive the apprenticeship directly there, then
you eliminate three of them forever, for the
first time in billions of
lifetimes, and if you eliminate these three,
then you will achieve citizenship within seven lifetimes,
no question,
guaranteed, so it is important what goes into
the  3. Give me one of these.
Doubts about Buddha. Two plans. Lady
Alexandra told me that he
debated with one of you. Prove
more that the brother exists and
most Buddhists have or have never
seen him.
But if you are the majority of the way,
only then will you see where. Then you will see
the rudder.
And then Peschel says, "I have the
psychological bestseller of the year."
If you get angry, just let it out.
Yes, I like his book. I am grateful,
but I was met yesterday.
I don't need it.
I have or seen or
understood.
I have learned that what or
teaches is correct.
I have directly experienced. I love you.
I appreciate it very much that you want to give me a book.
I have just met a human being, a person, who
can perceive everything at once from all times, from
everywhere in this universe, and I
think I will stick with it. So, the
first thing is, there is no more doubt
after the teaching time, having directly experienced it for the first time,
you understand that
the pen is not created by the pen.
But after the direct experience of the
teacher, the pen still looks like it did
on another side.
But you can remember what
you learned, you
learned directly that there's no pen that comes
from the other side. The third one is
called something similar to
yoga practice. There was an old yoga practice where it said that
if you want to go to Nirvana,
you should get a trident
and then stick the ground
with the three tines pointing upwards.
Then you stand on a chair and then you
're with God, and then you jump on
the three tines, and if the 13th tine
hits exactly here and here and here,
then you'll be enlightened. And there was
another practice: five fires lit
[music]
and you sit between them for a
week or so, then you're a
spiritual person. Or you hold your
hand up for ten years
and the hand and torso together, which is quite
nice, and you're a spiritual
person. And they're just stupid ideas.
After you've experienced the majority directly,
you can't believe in
these methods anymore. If someone comes to me now and
says, "I don't like doing things
with other people because then..."  I have
nothing left, why did
you
waste Lee with schoolbags? I thought you
liked shots, why did you give half to
Stanley?
This is wrong, and they think then
about the idea of ​​this with this lion
attitude, and that is the meaning
[music],
and that is the lion attitude, and now
I'll tell you what else he
says. When the body was done, the dance of the
lion, then they recognize the
wheel. The one who just saw the lion, the
colors, the lion punch, burned, godfather,
now the wheel,
they see again, it turns, and
we also see how to stop it.
That is usually the poem, very, very
difficult. I'll tell you again
who was done, who reached this meditation,
the meditation of the
lion's pledge, and then they recognize the wheel
will turn and how to
stop it, and then they go to the deep
stages of meditation, and this
includes the meditation of the end, which
comes, and they travel in time,
travel in time, and they play with it.  The
spirit of the world, they play with the spirit
of the world, they touch what is not
meditation,
they rise and they fall,
it is all touched, appears completely
meaningless, how many lines
deal with v  On the wheel,
one or two, you see the wheel will turn,
and how to stop it.
For 1700 years, a break. Web books about
these two lines. Is that cool?
Every time you study the wheel in the monastery, they
begin with these two
lines:
you see the wheel turning, and how to
stop it. And I thought,
maybe you know what the dance of
life is. It's
complicated. I'll give
you the explanation from London
Chamber Bonn. The apprenticeship ring is
called like vacation or the break because it's
called the big book, and this is a
book about Leer Heid by Tim K.,
the student of Kappa.
In this depiction of the wheel, there is
something that the body ride was realizing at the
moment when the
apprenticeship experience is over. And Mainz
describes what happens when
the direct experience of the majority has just
ended.
Here, Wasmeier is talking. While
you are still in meditation,
you can be like a lion. And while Otto
Preis,
we're talking about it differently now.
I'll tell you now, every day is when
you are in the apprenticeship.  Direct drive
typically serves the clan of a
lama, so exactly when they get up and
do the p for the lama, they
meditate every day for at least an
hour,
they study with their teachers
regularly, look after these teachers, and
they serve the community,
they help the community, the elderly, the sick, the
imprisoned, the
environment, they do something for the
community.
The four reasons that the majority
drive more directly are because they do these four things.
Then they would be making tea.
Suddenly, there is this trigger. Something is
triggered in the head in May.
Whether Cordes is not a pot on the stove,
it is only a silver thing and a
round shape. Tenor colors and shapes that
Mainau has kicked.
A white, black stick. It is not a
pen, it is only a stick, black,
white. Why both eyes can only see shapes and
colors. The eye cannot
decide what kind of thing it is. There are things at the back of the eye. They
receive a change in color and
a change in shape. They
cannot decide if it
is a pen or a toy.
So, he begs, this guy who has all the
prerequisites, they don't meditate, they don't
study for hours,
the sardines and the community,
and for these reasons, and then
they realize that the pot is an image in the
back of their mind, in their own head, and
this image comes from a farm in
your mind, and that forms the light,
and the mind transfers this image onto
this silver thing, and for the first
time,
they, as well as Karl May, in your mind, matures, for
the first time in billions of
lifetimes,
you recognize it, and then you bring it to
Lama Bin T,
you go to the temple and do a
daily meditation, and you sit down,
and now something really, really
cool happens, and the mind goes up through the
meditation levels like
climbing a ladder very quickly, it feels
like climbing walls,
the mind boom boom boom boom boom boom, and
when do you reach this level 3?
That's not the majority directly
experienced;
it means that in a meditation,
you reach higher levels,
the meditation performs boom boom boom
Boom boom, and then you reach
a platform, and from there
it goes into the direct experience of
the learning period,
and then maybe fifteen or
twenty minutes
you lose all sense of time,
you lose all sense of yourself,
you are aware that Doom
edits, you are simply in a
higher reality, and that is instructive,
and since the strange names for it run
out very quickly, it's usually just
20 minutes over, and my
fresh poultry was warm, was mbamba. You
come back down and you are still
in meditation,
but you no longer experience the majority,
and then you really have a meadow above
normal experiences, it's
not about majority.
I have the people in the squad of you
can see the day you die, you
see the day you become
brotherhood, you see yourself as
or directly as if you, your eyes are still like that,
and then the pen comes
from you,
it is time, just as
time is, so is the place, that
teacher, the time you spend with your
girlfriend in the car, when you  16
passes very quickly,
you stop kissing and then
it's already 2 a.m. Will
he be angry with you,
the time thieves at the dentist? It passes
slowly, the guy, board and board,
cutting and cutting and hammering and
filling, and eventually you're done, and somehow it
was only half an hour.
When you finish the direct experience of the
apprenticeship,
boom boom boom boom boom,
then one after the other, like a
fast slideshow, you see the faces of
all living beings in this universe, one
after the other in about five
minutes, and then something else happens:
you realize that you will take care of each and every one of them,
and that you will do
other things. An hour later, then
you end the meditation, get up and
walk around,
then there are a few left, stay
cool,
read other people's thoughts all day long, and when you
go to bed, then everything is over the next morning,
and that's why we're talking about it now,
because we're talking about the lion,
we're trying to find out what
Reh means.  On the 1st,
we try to find out who Rudd is talking about
when he speaks about the dance of the
lion, and quickly Tsonga
with students 600 years ago, he said
while you are in meditation,
you do this lion place,
and we call it in the time after,
in the following hours, the sods, the
Wheel of Life directly, when you study the Wheel
of Life from the new trainer, he is
not only interested in the Wheel of
Life,
he says some experience the Wheel of
Life directly, those who have just
come down from deep
meditation, make the deal, he has seen it directly,
and when you talk about who represents the wheel,
then you only talk about
people who
experienced the teaching time directly two or five minutes before,
there you have the laser pointer with you, I'll
tell you something interesting,
this is the Wheel of Difficulties,
everything when you are in the wheel, what has
died,
it is suffering, what it is, the first link in the
chain with understanding, what is the image
for this,
the blind man, Manfred Wassel, is
being blind, from this wheel, twelve cars,
club after the other
What causes the misunderstanding? The
next link of the potters, he makes the
karma. It's not just any kind of
karma. It's sending pens. What if that's
projecting karma? What does
projecting mean? That it projects a
new life within life in the council. It
projects another suffering. Life
born in blood and tears. Live a
long life and you'll see many
tragedies. Gather money, make babies, and
then lose everything, and the babies will
lose everything too.
That's the Wheel of Two, the second link.
[Music]
That's the karma that projects a new life in the
council. Which people
in the world don't make pots?
Aria, someone who has directly experienced the apprenticeship.
These are the only
people who aren't blind. So if
they don't make pots again, have
they already freed themselves from the council? Not yet,
and why not?
We still have some old pots
lying around,
but they are never more pots. The
remaining countries, Obama as a
maximum of seven lives, and that the money
in the explanation of mantra about the  The Wheel
of Life is there are many other
books, but the cool thing about Meyer's
explanation is that he talks about how to
go in and how to get out,
and this is what we'll call the Fan of the
Lion. And
I thought, now that
we're ready to start the class,
I thought he'd love to listen to
what the Panzer Lion
is and how to practice.
I think I have to continue the class tonight.
Is that okay? We
'll go through the text from 3 onwards,
his description of how to perform the Fan of the
Lion, how to
climb up, how to get back down, because
you have to go up so you
can directly experience the learning. And
which book to study, who it is from Peter's
explanation.
He says we don't have much time left,
but let's at least start.
He says, "Heal the verse in two parts"
[Music],
and to do that, we have to
print out the rest in the verses.
Here's the first one in Tibetan. In the
monastery, we had to
memorize it, of course. I forgot,
can I go first? The
meditation, the dance.  The lion's,
these are the first two lines. Then
you will see the wheel as it turns
and how it stops. And the
parts are two parts on YouTube, and
Jacob, now you are still meditating, and
Jacob breaks time after the mini-
station. In time, when you
have just finished the meditation,
you see the wheel turning and stopping
in the first two lines.
So, in general, you can
assume that the experience of the
wheel happens after the meditation, and
the dance of the lion happens in the
meditation. Which person has it?
And let's talk. Please concentrate for
five more minutes, and then
we'll take the photo. Now we're talking about the
dance of the lion. The ingredient spoken by Lord Mother
divides the Bob construction stop into eight
steps. These eight stages of
meditation are also called the eight
freedoms. They are not freedoms, but they are
called freedoms. And above that, there is
a ninth stage, and so
it's about laws. It's one
minute in real time, and he explains it
now in great detail on the more than ten
pages
there.  He says you will know what the
Dance of the Lion is; it is the eight
freedoms and a total of nine
stages of meditation. And then he says the second part,
after you come out, describes more of the
day for all of you. You should
study this wheel,
how each link triggers the next, and
how it turns around, how you put it in
reverse, like a car, how
you know the car back.
And then there is a famous
comment from H.D. Batra, in which he says
the Yogi Bear, the apprenticeship, goes more directly.
They go through the eight freedoms and
the new stages of meditation, and that is called
the Dance of the Lion.
And when you come out,
and when you then go into the following
thought,
why do they call it the Dance of the Lion?
Because a lion, and also the grandfather
rattlesnake, there is nothing that
can instill great fear when the
doubts of the pharmaceutical come to them, when
someone gives them the next book on
psychology, and when the pen says, "
I am a pen, I am a pen, I
come from my side, I come from..."  From
my side, I
now understand that this means the
lion at this point,
how can it be that I don't believe
that ACTA Tech, he says, when the middle
finger comes, right here he says that,
and we are not afraid to
look ahead and work through the obstacles to become
my brother,
why? Because they have tasted what it
is,
they have seen how time and place
collapse due to the desire, Jogi,
they know what it's like to see all living beings in
this universe within five
minutes,
they can, they can't eat, don't make it happen
if they want to,
only a Buddha can do that, but they know
how it feels and they know it's
possible,
we are not afraid of the rest of the
journey,
hey, are 500 years of meditating and
working too much,
no,
and that means the lion fans,
who said that, capture that, because of it,
or the lion dance, called the
flower place, taken,
and when we come out, then they see
the wheel, nobody teaches them the wheel,
they take it because they don't
always wait anymore, find, understood, well,
they're still in it, but they are
already
That's why we can see outside, and
we'll continue this evening.